fwd made insurance receive greater value
when you choose to buy direct from fwd
our innovative fwd made insurance
provides comprehensive coverage for your
helper greater convenience and
protection from unexpected events
caring for the person who cares for your
family
fwd offers cashless outpatient medical
expenses for your helper we're simply
using our medical e-card we cover up to
30 dollars per visit
subsidized checkups for mom's mandatory
six monthly examination is also
available
we also provide coverage for your
helpers pre-existing conditions at no
extra cost if she's been working in
singapore for more than 12 consecutive
months
protecting you from unexpected events
in the event that a replacement is
needed you're protected with a 100
refund on policy cancellation within the
first three months
we pay mom the security bond directly
without additional payment from you
[Music]
with security bond plus fwd is also the
only insurer that does not make you pay
if your bond gets forfeited by mom
fwd made insurance that protects you and
your family it's super easy to buy
online get a quote in 10 seconds today
[Music]
you